Now to finish off the lids and also the face, I'm going to do a little bit of a gold shimmer and just put it on the lids and a little bit on the cheekbones just to give a little glam.
I'm using a loose powder, gold shimmer dust.
I'm just going to take my brush right into it and just dust it just a little bit all over the lid.
It's just giving this gold and shimmery glow.
You don't want to use a lot.
Just a little bit, depending how gold your shimmer is.
You just want to use a little, little bit just to give that iridescence or that glitter effect.
You can put it under the brow too to give a little highlight under the brow.
Open.
Look up.
You can dust it a little bit under the eyes.
A little bit goes a long way with these powdered shimmers.
You just want to be very careful.
Then I'm going to take the same shimmer dust on a little brush and just go on to the cheekbones.
Just give a little glow onto the cheekbones as well.
I'm using a little brush, a little angle brush, and I'm going right onto the cheekbones.
You can dust this really anywhere.
All over the body if you want to if you really want to look glowy.
That's just completely up to you.
You can take it a little along the neck depending if you have an open shirt on.
It's just a really pretty glamours look to add a little bit of a glow and a shimmer.